export const PROBLEMS = {
    basicOperations: {
        question1: {
            question: "What's 7 + 7?",
            choice1: "8",
            choice2: "0",
            choice3: "14",
            choice4: "12",
            correctAns: "14"
        }, 
        question2: {
            question: "What's 3 + 2?",
            choice1: "7",
            choice2: "3",
            choice3: "2",
            choice4: "5",
            correctAns: "5"
        }, 
        question3: {
            question: "What's 9 - 3?",
            choice1: "7",
            choice2: "2",
            choice3: "6",
            choice4: "11",
            correctAns: "6"
        }, 
        question4: {
            question: "What's 25 + 5?",
            choice1: "30",
            choice2: "40",
            choice3: "25",
            choice4: "35",
            correctAns: "30"
        }, 
        question5: {
            question: "What's 17 - 3?",
            choice1: "12",
            choice2: "8",
            choice3: "14",
            choice4: "9",
            correctAns: "14"
        }, 
        question6: {
            question: "What's 1 + 7 - 4?",
            choice1: "5",
            choice2: "4",
            choice3: "6",
            choice4: "9",
            correctAns: "4"
        }, 
        question7: {
            question: "What's 13 - 10 + 20?",
            choice1: "23",
            choice2: "18",
            choice3: "25",
            choice4: "22",
            correctAns: "23"
        }, 
        question8: {
            question: "Ron has 17 apples. He eats 5. How many are left?",
            choice1: "10",
            choice2: "12",
            choice3: "11",
            choice4: "9",
            correctAns: "12"
        }, 
        question9: {
            question: "There are 8 slices of pizza. Bob eats 2 slices, Amy eats 5. How many are left?",
            choice1: "3",
            choice2: "1",
            choice3: "2",
            choice4: "0",
            correctAns: "1"
        }, 
        question10: {
            question: "2 bushes are in a field. 9 grow the next day but 1 dies. How many are left?",
            choice1: "8",
            choice2: "10",
            choice3: "12",
            choice4: "13",
            correctAns: "10"
        }, 
    },

    moreOperations: {
        question1: {
            question: "What is 7 x 5?",
            choice1: "20",
            choice2: "35",
            choice3: "45",
            choice4: "50",
            correctAns: "35"
        }, 
        question2: {
            question: "What is 8 x 12?",
            choice1: "96",
            choice2: "64",
            choice3: "86",
            choice4: "94",
            correctAns: "96"
        }, 
        question3: {
            question: "What is 100 ÷ 25?",
            choice1: "6",
            choice2: "4",
            choice3: "2",
            choice4: "5",
            correctAns: "4"
        }, 
        question3: {
            question: "What is 10 ÷ 2?",
            choice1: "2",
            choice2: "5",
            choice3: "1",
            choice4: "4",
            correctAns: "5"
        }, 
        question4: {
            question: "What is 12 ÷ 6?",
            choice1: "2",
            choice2: "1",
            choice3: "3",
            choice4: "0",
            correctAns: "2"
        }, 
        question5: {
            question: "What is 20 x 20?",
            choice1: "16",
            choice2: "40",
            choice3: "160",
            choice4: "400",
            correctAns: "400"
        },
        question6: {
            question: "What is 10 x 8?",
            choice1: "16",
            choice2: "80",
            choice3: "70",
            choice4: "400",
            correctAns: "80"
        }, 
        question7: {
            question: "What is 639 ÷ 639?",
            choice1: "22",
            choice2: "1",
            choice3: "639",
            choice4: "0",
            correctAns: "1"
        },
        question8: {
            question: "What is 69 ÷ 1?",
            choice1: "13",
            choice2: "1",
            choice3: "69",
            choice4: "0",
            correctAns: "69"
        }, 
        question9: {
            question: "What is 57 x 1?",
            choice1: "87",
            choice2: "62",
            choice3: "57",
            choice4: "114",
            correctAns: "57"
        },
        question10: {
            question: "What is 912 x 0?",
            choice1: "2",
            choice2: "34",
            choice3: "0",
            choice4: "12",
            correctAns: "0"
        },
        question11: {
            question: "Jack buys 8 ducks for $4 each. How much does he spend?",
            choice1: "$24",
            choice2: "$32",
            choice3: "$42",
            choice4: "$2",
            correctAns: "$32"
        },
        question12: {
            question: "Ryan has 7 packs of cola. Each pack has 6 colas. How many colas does he have?",
            choice1: "36",
            choice2: "26",
            choice3: "42",
            choice4: "38",
            correctAns: "42"
        },
        question13: {
            question: "Yotam shares 16 rocks equally between 4 people. How many rocks does each person get?",
            choice1: "12",
            choice2: "64",
            choice3: "4",
            choice4: "6",
            correctAns: "4"
        },
        question14: {
            question: "Maria the chicken has 30 seeds. She evenly stores them in 6 boxes. How many seeds are in each box?",
            choice1: "6",
            choice2: "5",
            choice3: "11",
            choice4: "8",
            correctAns: "5"
        },
        question15: {
            question: "Zack sells 4 pies for $6 each. He then splits the money between him and 7 friends. How much money does each person get?",
            choice1: "$4",
            choice2: "$3",
            choice3: "$6",
            choice4: "$1",
            correctAns: "$3"
        },
    },
    
    decimalsFractions: {

    },

    review1: {
        question1: {
            question: "What is 7 x 5?",
            choice1: "20",
            choice2: "35",
            choice3: "45",
            choice4: "50",
            correctAns: "35"
        }, 
        question2: {
            question: "What is 8 x 12?",
            choice1: "96",
            choice2: "64",
            choice3: "86",
            choice4: "94",
            correctAns: "96"
        }, 
    },

    //²³⁴
    advancedOperations: {
        question1: {
            question: "What is 3²?",
            choice1: "9",
            choice2: "2",
            choice3: "6",
            choice4: "1",
            correctAns: "9"
        }, 
        question2: {
            question: "What is 2³?",
            choice1: "2",
            choice2: "6",
            choice3: "8",
            choice4: "7",
            correctAns: "8"
        },
        question3: {
            question: "What is √9?",
            choice1: "9",
            choice2: "18",
            choice3: "3",
            choice4: "2",
            correctAns: "3"
        }, 
        question4: {
            question: "What is √36?",
            choice1: "17",
            choice2: "4",
            choice3: "6",
            choice4: "10",
            correctAns: "6"
        }, 
        question5: {
            question: "√19²",
            choice1: "12",
            choice2: "19",
            choice3: "21",
            choice4: "25",
            correctAns: "19"
        }, 
    },
}